It is easy as to understand the spread of our data visually.
من السهل فهم انتشار البيانات من الناحية البصرية.
The most common visual for quantitative data is known as a histogram.
يُعرف الشكل المرئي الأكثر شيوعًا للبيانات الكمية باسم المدرج التكراري.
In this video, we will take a look at exactly how histograms are constructed.
في هذا الفيديو، سنلقي نظرة على كيفية تكوين المدرجات التكرارية بالضبط.
In order to understand how histograms are constructed,
لفهم كيفية بناء المدرجات التكرارية،
consider we have the following data-set.
ضع في اعتبارك أن لدينا مجموعة البيانات التالية.
First, we need to bin our data.
أولًا، نحتاج إلى تخزين بياناتنا.
You as the histogram creator ultimately choose how the binning occurs.
يمكنك باعتبارك منشئ المدرج التكراري اختيار كيفية إجراء عملية التخزين.
Here, I have chosen our bins as one to four,
هنا، اخترت حاوياتنا الخاصة في صورة واحد إلى أربعة،
five to eight, 9-12 and 13-16.
وخمسة إلى ثمانية، و9-12، و13-16.
Because these first four values are between one and four,
ونظرًا لأن هذه القيم الأربع الأولى تتراوح بين واحد وأربعة،
they go into the first bin.
فإنها تذهب إلى الحاوية الأولى.
These next three values are between five and eight,
هذه القيم الثلاث التالية هي بين خمسة وثمانية،
so they fall in the next bin,
لذا فهي تقع في الحاوية التالية،
then these two values fall in this bin and 15 falls into our last bin.
ثم تقع هاتان القيمتان في هذه الحاوية و15 تقع في الحاوية الأخيرة.
The number of values in each bin determine the height of each histogram bar.
يحدد عدد القيم في كل حاوية ارتفاع كل شريط مدرج تكراري.
Changing the bins will result in a slightly different visual.
سيؤدي تغيير الحاويات إلى رؤية بصرية مختلفة قليلًا.
There really isn't a right answer to choosing our bins,
ليس هناك في الحقيقة إجابة صحيحة لاختيار حاوياتنا،
and in most cases software will choose the appropriate bins for us.
وفي معظم الحالات، سوف يختار البرنامج الحاويات المناسبة لنا.
But it is something to be aware of.
ولكن هذا شيء يجب أن تدركه.